bestadvisor.com 2018-09-03

# 

This Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy") governs the manner in which [info@bestadvisor.com](mailto:info@bestadvisor.com) collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of info@bestadvisor.com website (together with its subdomains, content and services, the "Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all services offered by the Site.

### Access/Accuracy

We provide individuals the right to access and to correct, if necessary, their personal data which we process. If you have any queries or complaints, or wish to exercise your rights as detailed above, please contact us at: [info@bestadvisor.com](mailto:info@bestadvisor.com) To the extent that you do provide us with Personal Information, we wish to maintain accurate Personal Information. If you would like to delete or correct any inaccuracy in your Personal Information that we may be storing, or otherwise amend or delete your Personal Information, you may submit a request by sending an email to [info@bestadvisor.com](mailto:info@bestadvisor.com) Your email should include adequate details of your request.

### Children's Privacy

The Site is not structured to attract children under the age of 13 years. Accordingly, we do not intend to collect Personal Information from anyone we know to be under 13 years. If we learn that we have collected Personal Information from a child under 13 years, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any such information, please contact us at [info@bestadvisor.com](mailto:info@bestadvisor.com).

### Your California Privacy Rights

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits Users who are California residents to request certain information regarding its disclosure of Personal Information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an email to [info@bestadvisor.com](mailto:info@bestadvisor.com). Please note that we are only required to respond to one request per customer each year.

### Your Acceptance Of These Terms

This Privacy Policy forms part of the Site’s Terms of Use, available at bestadvisor.com/terms (the "Terms"). By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy and the processing of Personal Information for the purposes set forth herein. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

### Contacting Us

This document was last updated on December 11, 2015
